[
    {
        "categoria": "suma",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 + 3?",
        "respuesta": "8",
        "incorrecta1": "6",
        "incorrecta2": "10",
        "incorrecta3": "7",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "division",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 10 / 2?",
        "respuesta": "5",
        "incorrecta1": "3",
        "incorrecta2": "10",
        "incorrecta3": "2",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "multiplicación",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 * 3?",
        "respuesta": "15",
        "incorrecta1": "8",
        "incorrecta2": "12",
        "incorrecta3": "2",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "suma",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 - 1?",
        "respuesta": "5",
        "incorrecta1": "6",
        "incorrecta2": "7",
        "incorrecta3": "10",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "suma",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 + 2?",
        "respuesta": "9",
        "incorrecta1": "5",
        "incorrecta2": "10",
        "incorrecta3": "8"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "resta",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 12 - 4?",
        "respuesta": "8",
        "incorrecta1": "6",
        "incorrecta2": "10",
        "incorrecta3": "2"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "multiplicación",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 * 3?",
        "respuesta": "12",
        "incorrecta1": "7",
        "incorrecta2": "10",
        "incorrecta3": "2"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "división",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 16 / 4?",
        "respuesta": "4",
        "incorrecta1": "8",
        "incorrecta2": "2",
        "incorrecta3": "6"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "suma",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 9 + 6?",
        "respuesta": "15",
        "incorrecta1": "13",
        "incorrecta2": "10",
        "incorrecta3": "12"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "resta",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 15 - 7?",
        "respuesta": "8",
        "incorrecta1": "10",
        "incorrecta2": "6",
        "incorrecta3": "9"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "multiplicación",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 * 9?",
        "respuesta": "18",
        "incorrecta1": "12",
        "incorrecta2": "7",
        "incorrecta3": "15"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "división",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 20 / 5?",
        "respuesta": "4",
        "incorrecta1": "10",
        "incorrecta2": "3",
        "incorrecta3": "6"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "suma",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 + 4?",
        "respuesta": "7",
        "incorrecta1": "6",
        "incorrecta2": "8",
        "incorrecta3": "5"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "resta",
        "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 10 - 3?",
        "respuesta": "7",
        "incorrecta1": "6",
        "incorrecta2": "5",
        "incorrecta3": "8"
    }
]